<Alloy>
    <View id='container'>
        <ScrollableView id='instructions'>
            <View class='wrap'>
                <Label class='heading'>Help Screens</Label>
                <Label class='content'>To see these help messages again, tap and hold anywhere. Swipe left to see the next help screen...</Label>
            </View>
            <View class='wrap'>
                <Label class='heading'>What Fixer Does</Label>
                <Label class='content'>Fixer will help you make corrections to the specific gravity of your wort by recommending a water or malt extract addition.</Label>
                <Label class='content'>Calculations are based upon target gravity, current gravity, temperature, and final wort volume...</Label>
            </View>
            <View class='wrap'>
                <Label class='heading'>When to use Fixer</Label>
                <Label class='content'>Fixer is most efficiently used after all wort has left the mash tun and immediately before beginning the boil...</Label>
            </View>
            <View class='wrap'>
                <Label class='heading'>Making Adjustments</Label>
                <Label class='content'>Slide your finger up and down the screen to make adjustments to gravity, temperature, or volume. Notice Fixer's change in recommendation as you modify the wort's properties...</Label>
            </View>
            <View class='wrap'>
                <Label class='heading'>Changing Units</Label>
                <Label class='content'>Tap any unit of measurement to change it's value. Gallons changes to Litres, Pounds to Kilograms, Dry Malt Extract to Liquid Malt Extract...</Label>
            </View>
            <View class='wrap'>
                <Label class='heading'>How it Works</Label>
                <Label class='content'>Fixer's formula is inspired by a Homebrew Stackexchange question. It uses a combination of Brewery.org's hydrometer correction as well as basic gravity and volume formulas which can be found in many homebrew text books...</Label>
                <Label class='link content' id='se_link'>→ Stack Exchange Article</Label>
                <Label class='link content' id='borg_link'>→ Brewery.org</Label>
            </View>
            <View class='wrap'>
                <Label class='heading'>Calibration</Label>
                <Label class='content'>Fixer's formula anticipates a hydrometer calibration of 60°F.</Label>
                <Label class='content'>I felt this was a normal level and would work for most people. If you feel otherwise, please let me know...</Label>
            </View>
            <View class='wrap'>
                <Label class='heading'>Contact</Label>
                <Label class='content'>If you have ideas to make this app better, or concepts for future homebrewer applications, I'd love to hear about them.</Label>
                <Label class='link content' id='email'>→ Email Joe Longstreet</Label>
            </View>
        </ScrollableView>
        <Label id='close'>×</Label>
    </View>
</Alloy>