<Alloy>
    <View id='container'>
        <ScrollableView id='instructions'>
            <View class='wrap'>
                <Label class='heading'>1.014 Fixer</Label>
                <Label class='content'>Fixer will help you make corrections to the specific gravity of your wort immediately before entering the boil. You'll need to know the target gravity, current gravity, temperature, and final volume...</Label>
            </View>
            <View class='wrap'>
                <Label class='heading'>Adjustments</Label>
                <Label class='content'>Slide your finger up and down the screen to make adjustments to gravity, temperature, or volume. Notice Fixer's change in recommendation as you modify the wort's properties...</Label>
            </View>
            <View class='wrap'>
                <Label class='heading'>Units</Label>
                <Label class='content'>Tap any unit of measurement to change it's value. Gallons turns to Litres, Pounds to Kilograms, Dry Malt Extract to Liquid Malt Extract...</Label>
            </View>
            <View class='wrap'>
                <Label class='heading'>Help</Label>
                <Label class='content'>To see these help messages again, tap and hold anywhere on screen. To learn more about how Fixer works, please swipe to the next screen...</Label>
            </View>
            <View class='wrap'>
                <Label class='heading'>How it Works</Label>
                <Label class='content'>There are a few extra things going on with Fixer, but for the most part, the formula follows the pattern described in the linked article...</Label>
                <Label class='link content' id='link'>Link</Label>
            </View>
            <View class='wrap'>
                <Label class='heading'>Calibration</Label>
                <Label class='content'>Fixer uses a formula which anticipates a hydrometer calibration of 60°F. I felt this was a normal level and would work for most people. If you feel otherwise, please let me know.</Label>
            </View>
            <View class='wrap'>
                <Label class='heading'>Contact</Label>
                <Label class='content'>If you have ideas to make this app better, or concepts for future homebrewer applications, I'd love to hear about them.</Label>
                <Label class='link content' id='email'>Email Joe Longstreet</Label>
            </View>
        </ScrollableView>
        <Label id='close'>×</Label>
    </View>
</Alloy>